Hey.
Heeju.
Huh?
What the hell?
Shit.
That's enough.
Just put the gold in the car.
Hey, you're messing with me.
It's not loaded, right?
Shut up and don't say anything!
The gold. Put it in the back of the car.
Okay. I'll do it.
CHAIRMAN AHN GYUSEOK INCOMING CALL
Yes, Chairman.
Did you find the casket?
Not yet. I'm close, though, sir.
Didn't you say you found out who the accomplice was?
Lee Dokyung's girl.
Yes, that's right.
I'm actually after her right now, sir. Don't worry.
I'm on it.
- I'll make sure to find the gold no- -  Gold?
Fuck me.
- Chief Cheon. -  Yes, sir.
Can we wrap things up here today?
Yes, sir. We're almost done.
Tie up any loose ends now.
We're going to Jeongsan tomorrow. :cue
Yes, Chairman.
EPISODE 6 FISSURE
INCLINED SHAFT 8, SECTION 0 100ML
Ah, shit. This is fucking hard.
Heeju!
Ah, this is the last of it.
If you had done this by yourself,
ah, I bet it would have taken all day.
Okay.
Now we just need to take care of Cha Yujin, right?
Then no one else knows.
You know about it now, too.
Come on. It's me.
Heeju.
I just want my share. That's all.
Okay, so now we just make potatoes and sell them just like before.
Sound good? I'll still sell them.
Okay.
There. You can check the gold bars.
Hmm?
Yeah?
Okay?
So, we good?
Don't come any closer.
Really?
You said Cha Yujin is on her way.
You think you can kill her by yourself?
I'll kill her for you, yeah?
Just like I got rid of Han Cheoljung for you.
I can do it myself.
Now move.
- Over there? - Just shut up!
-  Okay, okay! - Move out of the way.
Turn around.
Come on.
Heeju, please don't do this.
- Turn around. -  Heeju.
L-let's talk about this, okay?
You and me. We're in this together.
Yeah?
Hey, I saved your life, didn't I?
But what? You still don't trust me?
I can't trust anyone.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, how about this?
I didn't see anything.
I never saw a single gold bar. I wasn't here.
- I told you to turn around! -  Okay, okay, okay, okay!
Heeju, please.
Please, just calm down.
Please don't do this. Please?
You know I'm always on your side, right?
Even if everyone else betrays you, I could never do that to you!
Please just trust me, 'kay?
Just fucking shoot me, then!
But Kim Heeju...
...if you do, I fucking swear that you'll die right here with me, too.
Dammit.
Fuck.
Take all of that cash and the rest of the potatoes.
That should be enough to cover your share.
Shouldn't it? Now go.
What about you?
I can take care of myself.
Don't come looking for me.
Forget about everything you saw here.
And move on with your life.
If I ever see you again, I don't know.
I might actually shoot you. :cue
DAD! BE SAFE AGAIN TODAY
INCLINED SHAFT 8, SECTION 0 100ML
- You're sure? - Please! Come on, just go! Go!
Shit!
Call me if you need anything.
'Kay?
I'm going. Okay?
Dammit.
Oh, shit. Who's that?
Fuck it, who cares? Let's get outta here!
Who the fuck is that?
What do we do?
Dammit, who...
- Is that the boss? - Huh?
Ah, fuck!
- Dammit, we're fucked. -  What do we do? What do we do?
We're fucking fucked.
Fuck!
Look out!
Wait.
It's Cha Yujin's car.
She's dead.
What?
Give me the gun.
Park might have seen us. We have no other choice.
We gotta kill the guy.
Just give it to me.
Wait!
Just stay here!
I'll be right back.
Shit.
Fuck.
:cue
Shit!
Ah, shit.
Shit.
Dammit.
TEAM LEADER CHA YUJIN OUTGOING CALL
Bitch!
YANGPO JEIL HOSPITAL
Ah, there.
Okay, can you try standing? Walking a little?
-  Yeah. - Careful.
You'll likely have some pain for a while so don't overdo it.
-  All right, we're all done here. -  Doctor.
What?
I'm very sorry about this.
Shit!
Could you please take me to downtown Yangpo?
Heeju, it's Dokyung. I escaped from the hospital.
Call me on this number. :cue
DIRECTOR PARK INCOMING CALL
Come on. Come on!
- Yeah. -  I need you to run a plate.
Blue-colored Santa Fe.
Last few digits, five, two, seven, nine.
No. What? Hey! Hey, waiter!
Hey!
- Whose is it? -  How the fuck would I know?
That's why I'm telling you to run the plates!
If you can find the car, even better.
Where's Cha Yujin now?
I checked the whole area but her Renegade wasn't there.
Your car was, though.
I lost her.
Did you kill her?
Just find the fucking Santa Fe!
Can you do it today?
I thought you wanted me to stay out of it.
Why do you keep doing this to me?
This is the last time.
The chairman, he gets back tomorrow.
Yeah, exactly. I'm done helping you.
If this thing goes wrong, I'll be the one taking the fall.
I'll give you 100 more gold chips.
The hell is this man talking about?
For fuck's sake, fucking bastard.
What'd I just say?
I'm not doin' it.
I bet you didn't even know Lee Dokyung escaped from the hospital,
did you? Detective Kang is about to call you.
I think you're fucked now, Park.
Think carefully, now.
This fucking asshole.
Fuck that detective.
Bastard.
Is Kim Heeju the only one left now?
Dammit.
WOOGY INCOMING CALL
- Yes? -  Hey, you fucking traitor!
You ran off to save your own skin, huh?
Some partner you are.
You said you were gonna kill Park Hocheol.
Yeah, no shit!
If you had just stayed there like I said instead of running away,
I could have killed him.
Did Park see your face?
I don't fucking know.
It was so dark in there, I don't know. I don't think so.
What-what about you?
I'm not sure. I think he might have seen me.
Ah, dammit.
Wait for me at the workshop, okay?
I'll go to the office tomorrow and see how things are going.
- Then I'll meet up with you. -  No.
I told you I never want to see you again.
What the fuck are you talking about, Heeju?
Things have changed now.
And my potatoes are still there in the back of your car!
I need those, you know.
Ah, shit.
Heeju, don't forget.
I'm from Yes Money.
I'll just leave it for you at the workshop.
Pick it up there.
Okay.
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, yeah, yeah. Heeju, Heeju. :cue
Have you heard anything from Lee Dokyung?
I haven't. Why?
Well, apparently he escaped from the fucking hospital.
Yes Money's looking for him, too.
Listen.
You need to hide the gold bars in a better spot.
And you better not tell anyone.
How the hell did Cha Yujin even find out the gold was in the mine, let alone Park?
Heeju, please. Don't trust anyone.
How many times do I have to fucking tell you,
don't trust anyone?
Especially Lee Dokyung. Got it?
HEEJU, THIS IS DOKYUNG. I ESCAPED FROM THE HOSPITAL. CALL ME AT THIS NUMBER.
Hello?
-  Dokyung? - Heeju, you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay. I'm doing fine.
How about you? You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm so glad.
I was so worried about you, Heeju.
How did you get out of the hospital?
I ran away.
Park found out where the casket was and I couldn't get a hold of you.
You got my message, right?
And you moved all the gold bars?
Actually, maybe we should talk in person.
Where are you now? I can come to you.
Uh, no, I'll come to you.
Where are you right now?
I'm still in Yangpo.
I'll meet you there.
Get a hotel room and then just send me a message.
Right now it's a bit dangerous, so I'll come by tonight.
Okay.
Uh, and hey, where are the gold bars now?
Let's meet first. I'll tell you about it then.
Okay.
What is this?
Ah, seriously?
You looking to buy a car, sir?
No, I'm here to talk to you, Heo Donggu.
Why do you wanna talk to me? I didn't do anything wrong.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's just go in the office, all right?
Oh, great. Shit.
RESIDENT REGISTRATION CARD JU HARAN
Ju Haran?
Not Kim Heeju?
Yeah.
Why, did she cause some kind of accident?
All I-all I did was sell her a car.
Anything else, I don't-I don't- I don't know anything about her.
Well, it's just a little weird. It was this woman, right?
- Yeah. -  It was?
-  Yeah. - Look. Different name.
So it wasn't Cha Yujin. It was Kim Heeju.
Wait. So then are the police looking for her,
or is it the people from Geumseong?
Was Park here? Park Hocheol?
Park Hocheol? That fucking asshole coming here?
No way! I'd kill that fucker if he shows his face here.
Sure he wouldn't kill you?
Hey, man, you haven't seen me throw a punch, have you?
I'd take him down. What, y-you think I'm some kind of weakling?
Punching doesn't really mean anything when Park Hocheol pulls a knife on you.
Hold on.
If Park Hocheol is involved, this is about Geumseong.
Did this woman you're looking for take something that belongs to them?
Just call me if you see Park Hocheol.
How many times do I have to say? I told you he wouldn't dare.
All right. Look, I get it.
You obviously don't like him at all. Wanna kill him, right?
Of course I do. You see what that prick did to my ear? :cue
HAENGBOK PAWNSHOP
Skyday, room 2014.
You can reach me at this number from now on.
23rd floor.
Doors closing.
100 ten-kilo gold bars?
Yes.
What's the source?
Cambodia.
Hold up. Is this about the recent leak?
Yeah.
So, it is stolen goods. That's bold.
Well, Interpol's lost the trace.
No records left in any account. It's clean.
At the price from two years ago, I'd say it's a win-win for both sides.
I would like to see the real thing first.
When are you coming over?
I will let you know.
Okay.
WHERE ARE YOU? ABOUT CAMBODIA...
INCOMING VOICE CALL
Heeju, where are you?
I just talked to the people who are gonna buy our gold.
We should be able to get a good price for all the bars.
Good job, Heeju.
It's over.
We can just start our new lives together.
You still there?
Heeju, did you hear me?
- I'm here. -  Okay.
You heard what I said, right?
They murdered Cha Yujin.
Yeah, I know.
That asshole Park called and tried to blackmail me.
But it's okay.
We've got nothing to worry about.
I have other contacts at airport security so moving the gold shouldn't be a problem.
Our Cambodian buyers said they'd help, too.
Cha Yujin told me everything.
About how you two used to be together.
It didn't mean anything, Heeju.
I don't know what she told you, but you're different.
It's different with us.
Sh-she's just-she's nothing to me.
Someone close to you just died.
And it's okay because someone else can help with shipping?
I guess you were right.
Cha Yujin really meant nothing to you at all.
That's what I was trying to tell you.
No one else matters.
:cue
You're different from all of them.
I think I've gone too far.
Where are you now? I can come find you.
I don't think I can see you today.
I'm sorry. I'll call you later.
Wait.
GANGWON SAEBAEK HOSPITAL
What have you been doing?
Auntie.
Let me sleep here just tonight.
I'm so tired.
That's what it is.
You smell like a coal mine.
That damp coal smell.
The one that miners have on their clothes.
JEIL WORKSHOP
Hoonseok?
You brought it.
Yeah.
And the rest of the gold bars.
Where are they?
Tell me.
Where did you hide the gold bars? :cue
I'm gonna shoot.
Three.
Two.
One.
Good.
Good, you got it now. No matter what happens,
you never tell anybody where the bars are.
Seriously, Heeju, if I wanted to I could've just...
...I mean, how the hell could you even think of betraying me like that?
Look.
This potato's what saved your life.
So did you meet up with Lee Dokyung?
I didn't.
Why not?
Because I can't trust anyone.
Not anymore.
Wait a sec.
So you're not going with Lee Dokyung? Did you end things?
Yes! Good job, Heeju! You finally got it!
Hell, you can't trust a guy like him!
Heh, I was trying to tell you that this whole time, and I-
wait a minute.
The thing is, you still have all the gold bars.
Is Dokyung really just gonna walk away?
Ah, shit. Do I need to kill him?
Don't think that I trust you, either.
Okay.
Be that way.
You just use me.
Keep on using me.
As much as you want.
Happy to be of service.
For every two ten-kilo bars, I get one one-kilo bar.
Just one.
Not too much, right?
Oh, yeah. That reminds me.
I did the math and it should take us about six months to sell them all.
Six.
Park knows about me now.
That means soon your whole company will, too.
Not to mention the police on top of that.
And you're telling me we have to last six more months?
No. They don't know.
Park? He doesn't know.
Cha Yujin must have told Park about me.
The gold bars, everything. He must know.
If Park had known it was you,
he wouldn't have gone to the mine.
He would have gone to the pawnshop.
So now here's the real question.
Park was alone. Why?
After he killed Cha Yujin,
he went to the mine alone without telling anyone.
Why did he do that?
Because that way...
- ...he could keep all the gold. - Bingo.
And he didn't want Chairman Ahn to find out.
Chairman Ahn?
The real owner of the gold.
Geumseong's chair, Ahn Gyuseok.
Chairman Ahn gets back to Korea today.
And that means Park is fucked.
Welcome back, Chairman.
Welcome back, sir!
These are our partners from Cambodia. Our executives.
- Introduce yourselves. - Yes, sir.
- Director Jo. - Thank you for coming all this way.
These guys here, take care of 'em.
- Nice to meet you. - Give them anything they want.
- You understand? Only the best. - Of course, sir.
This way, please.
- Come here. - Sir.
What is this?
Be more subtle.
Apologies. :cue
Hey, step on it.
My stomach is starting to hurt from all that greasy food I had to eat.
Do I really have to ask about it?
Right, yes.
- So, Lee Dokyung, he- - Managed to escape from the hospital.
You're kidding, right?
Why did I have to hear that from someone else?
It seemed like you had a busy schedule,
so I was planning to report it to you when you got back.
You do not make decisions for me.
Yes, sir.
So the casket.
Is it waiting for us at the hotel?
I'm sorry, sir.
Enough with the apologizing "I'm sorry" shit.
You should know me better than anyone else by now.
Have I ever said anything about all the bullshit,
or the way you all stab each other in the back?
There's only one thing I can't forgive.
And that's any damage to the company. I will not let that happen.
I take responsibility.
I'll find the casket, sir.
It's too late now.
H.S HOTEL & RESORT CONSTRUCTION
Huh, you know, maybe we dug a little too deep.
Hey, Park Hocheol.
Look where you are. Shit.
Think carefully, now.
How did you know what was in the casket?
Kim Jinman, he...
...he told me.
Ah.
So the police already found out about it.
And you decided not to tell me.
You didn't bring it up.
So that meant-
So that meant I couldn't-
I couldn't tell you.
That's not the reason.
Otherwise, you would have just asked me about it.
Were you planning to find it and take it for yourself?
Or did you already do it, and now you're lying?
Did you plan this with Lee Dokyung?
No. No, sir.
Right.
Because if you had, you wouldn't still be in Geumseong.
You probably would have fled already.
Stay out of the business with the casket.
Go back to Yes Money and keep doing what you used to do. :cue
Say hi to the shareholders at Gold Land.
Get 'em to sign that contract.
Yeah, the more I think about it, it's all you're really cut out for.
Get him out.
Fuck, I must be getting old now. I'm getting a bit soft, huh?
You know what?
You should have reported this whole thing right away.
Coulda avoided the Chairman's wrath.
You got pretty lucky in the end, though.
I mean, he wanted to cut your ear off.
I barely talked him out of it.
Mm, from now on,
you should keep your head down at Yes Money. Gimmie that.
I'll take care of the gold bars, okay? Here.
Come on, Park.
How did you know about the gold bars?
I was in Yangpo then, wasn't I?
I sent the casket. I've always known.
You've lost your fucking touch, you know know that?
You don't know your place.
Hey, here you go.
Good luck getting out of there!
Park isn't the only one.
I think someone else saw me, too.
What do you mean? Who saw you?
Kim Jinman.
I think he saw me getting into my car that night.
When I was running away from the Jeongsan nightclub with Cha Yujin.
Listen to me! Open the door!
Look, look, look! Roll, roll, roll down your window!
He must not have seen you 'cause he would have reported you
to my company right away.
Yeah, but you know...
...what if he's not saying anything because he wants the gold for himself?
Park never said anything, either.
Ah, shit.
Heeju.
Your old phone and credit card. You threw those away, right?
Then you got no choice.
You have to be Ju Haran for the rest of your life.
Don't worry about it.
If Detective Kim finds out...
...then I'll simply go and kill him for you.
Then you can give me an extra potato.
Deal? :cue
Hello.
Hi, there. Hey.
Uh, room five.
Was Yeo Sunok discharged already?
Uh, no. She was moved to a private room.
- She was? -  Yes.
Wow, so pretty!
Now, here.
Ah!
Oh, wow. What a nice room you got here.
- Huh? -  Sorry, who-
-  Must be pretty expensive. -  Who are you?
Oh.
Is he from the ER?
- Could you just give us a second? -  Hmm?
Oh.
This really is a nice room. Wow.
When were you put in here? Damn, look at this view.
Isn't it too expensive, though?
Why are you here?
Just wanted to say hi to an old friend.
Can't a guy do that?
Who knows? We might not have much time left.
I'm not just talkin' about you.
I mean, at our age, who doesn't have some kind of illness or some other kinda shit?
I got diabetes.
And my liver's not great, either.
I could go any day now, you know?
Hey.
Isn't it weird we both live in Jeongsan
but we've never run into each other before now?
More like we pretended not to.
I saw you a couple times.
Why didn't you say anything?
What's the point in that?
There's nothing left between us.
And your husband?
Has he come to see you?
No, he hasn't.
Well, still, doesn't seem like he's that bad of a guy.
I mean, he even dropped the charges...
If you're done saying hi, you should just go.
Instead of hanging around here, dredging up old memories.
Ah, come on, now. Don't be like that.
Oh, by the way. Who is Ju Haran?
I asked at the front desk and the receptionist said Ju Haran
is your guardian, but I thought it'd be Han Cheoljung.
I don't know.
What do you mean? It's your guardian.
Don't tell me you don't know.
Here, wait.
Look at this.
It's her.
Yeah.
Right?
Must be. Yeah.
I remember seeing her here the other day when I came to visit you.
It is her, right?
But then I thought,
"This woman's name is Kim Heeju, right?"
Who is she?
Your daughter?
No.
My niece.
Your niece?
I didn't know that you had a niece.
- I do. -  I see.
Oh, so then your niece, she must be pretty well-off, right?
She got you into this fancy room
and already took care of your hospital bills.
Where does she live?
Jeongsan?
When is she back?
I don't know.
She stopped by when she heard I was sick.
Why do you ask?
Why do you wanna know when she'll be here?
Well, you told me she's your niece, so I'd like to meet her.
What? Why?
Has she been gambling or something?
Is she in trouble?
No.
Then...
...did she murder someone or anything like that?
Come on. What an awful thing to say.
Nothing like that.
No, she just borrowed some money.
- How much was it? -  A lot.
Actually...
...it's not just about the money.
Though I'd hate for someone her age to end up with a criminal record.
It's not too late for her to pay it back.
Or if that's not possible,
then she could try and reach some kind of settlement at least.
Looks like she turned off her phone, and disappeared instead.
That's why I brought her up.
So if she calls you or comes to visit,
please be sure to let me know.
I'll be more than happy to help her settle the matter.
All right?
Don't tell her I was here, though.
If she knows the police are involved, she won't show up.
There's nothing to worry about, hmm? I won't do anything to your niece.
-  Call me, okay? -  Ms. Yeo Sunok?
I need to check your temperature.
:cue
Huh?
All right. I'll head out now.
You'll give me a call, right?
Yeah.
Take care of yourself. Get some rest.
Hey, Heeju. Where are you?
- Uh, Dokyung- -  Tell me where you are
and I'll come find you so we can talk.
I'm not really sure that's a good idea.
Do you think we can go back to how things used to be?
What do you mean?
Is it-is this because of the whole Cha Yujin thing
because I never told you about her?
You're right.
I took advantage of a woman I was dating, but Heeju...
...it's different with us.
I think that...
...I was actually the one taking advantage of you.
When we first met...
...I saw you as my only way out.
No, Heeju, it's okay. We can be happy like before.
That money will fix everything. What more could we need?
Yangpo is out.
They've tightened up security. It's too risky.
So I was thinking a boat might be our best bet.
We stowaway?
Mm-hmm.
I know someone who uses cargo ships to export cars.
How do you know them?
Turns out money can do anything.
Okay, then. Let's move as quickly as possible.
No, I'm not going with you.
You're going by yourself.
And the gold bars...
...we should split them.
What?
I...
I think I deserve at least that much. Don't you?
I risked my life to keep them hidden. So here's what we'll do.
On the day you head for Cambodia, I'll bring your share by car.
I'll bring your passport, too.
So you can just meet me at the port.
And you won't try and find the rest of the gold bars.
What? Heeju. What are you talking about?
Look, tell me where you are.
Can we please just talk about this in person?
Whatever you say.
We can just split the gold bars, if that's what you want.
But can we at least talk in person?
Where are you now?
Are you still staying at the pawnshop?
No, I'm not there anymore.
Don't go there.
And don't come looking for me, either.
Wait, Hee-Heeju.
INCOMING CALL
POWER OFF
Your call has been forwarded to an automated voice-
Fuck! Why are you doing this?
:cue
Boss.
I want to repay you for everything.
I know this isn't anything special, but I made it for you.
Here.
It's a four-leaf clover. It brings good luck.
So if you wear it then you'll be lucky.
Oh, I made it with my own share of the potatoes,
so you don't have to worry about that.
Is that true?
What?
If I keep this with me...
...will it really bring good luck, even to me?
Um, well, no.
It's just a superstition, of course.
But believing in things like that can still bring us comfort.
Thank you.
Take care of yourself, Heeju.
All right. So what'd he say?
By the way.
Heeju, do you have to go this far?
Just for Lee Dokyung?
I mean, you're helping with his travel.
And giving him half of the gold bars, too.
I just, I overheard you talking on the phone yesterday.
It's not like I meant to.
It was an accident! It was.
I went back to grab something I left and I heard you.
It really, really was an accident.
It was his to begin with.
I figured I should give him his share.
Lee Dokyung's share is half of the bars?
Really?
Heeju, do you-
do you still love that asshole?
Huh? Even after everything he did to you?
Didn't you break up already?
Yeah, we did.
We're breaking up.
But it's not like I want him to be unhappy.
What does that even mean?
Ugh, I don't know. Leave me alone.
It's my gold anyway.
No, it's mine, too!
Of those 100 gold bars, 5% belongs to me.
You're just gonna give half to Dokyung?
Okay, then.
You can have 10% of my share.
For every ten-kilo gold bar I cash in, you get a one-kilo bar.
Sound good?
Wait a minute. Let me just do the math.
Four, five, six, seven.
Ten billion?
I get ten billion?
Wow! Ten bill! Fuck me!
Is that enough for you?
That's all you've ever wanted? :cue
Why?
Will you give me more if I ask?
No, I was just wondering.
You'd do anything for money.
Yet you've been the least greedy.
Every other person around me has tried to steal everything I had.
Really? Huh. I, uh, never thought about it.
Hi, good evening. Did you order express delivery?
Yeah.
Okay.
HAENGBOK PAWNSHOP
Fuck.
Why are you here?
H-Heeju.
:cue
♪ Another day another hour ♪
♪ Free falling in my mind ♪
♪ I will find all of the reasons for leaving ♪
♪ When everyone around me's changing ♪
♪ Everyone but me ♪
♪ All the things I thought I could be ♪
♪ Are out of reach ♪
♪ I leave it all behind ♪
♪ As you fall in line ♪
♪ I'm not expecting any light at your door ♪
♪ There's nothing left ♪
♪ Just the pieces of everything we could have been before ♪
♪ Evermore ♪
♪ I don't feel it like I used to ♪
♪ Anymore ♪
♪ You could find me in the dark ♪
♪ Still calling through the night ♪
♪ I leave behind all of the seasons ♪
♪ I've dreamed of ♪
♪ But the water's rising over everything I've known ♪
♪ Drifting out here all alone ♪
♪ On your own ♪
♪ So leave it all behind ♪
♪ As you fall in line ♪
♪ I'm not expecting any light at your door ♪
♪ There's nothing left ♪
♪ Just the pieces of everything we could have been before ♪
♪ Evermore ♪
♪ I don't... ♪